{"data":[{"question":"Mumps are a very common disease which usually affects children.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"common disease","c":"which","d":"usually","answer":"1","explain":" - Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Nancy said that she went to the supermarket before coming home.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"went","c":"to","d":"before coming","answer":"2","explain":" - Went-> had gone","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Before she moved here, Arlene had been president of the organization since four years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Before","b":"been","c":"of the","d":"since","answer":"4","explain":" - Since-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Each of the nurses report to the operating room when his or her name is called.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of the","b":"report","c":"his or her name","d":"is called","answer":"2","explain":" - Report-> reports","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The athlete, together with his coach and several relatives, are traveling to the Olympic Games.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"athlete","b":"with","c":"his coach","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":" - Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Professor Duncan teaches both anthropology as well as sociology each fall.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"teaches","b":"both","c":"anthropology","d":"each fall","answer":"2","explain":" - Both-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"My brother is in California on vacation, but I wish he was here so that he could help me repair my car.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"on","c":"was","d":"me repair my car","answer":"3","explain":" - Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I certainly appreciate him telling us about the delay in delivering the materials because we had planned to begin work tomorrow.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"certainly","b":"him","c":"telling us","d":"delivering","answer":"2","explain":" him -> his","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The chemistry instructor explained the experiment in such of a way that it was easily understood.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"such of a way","c":"was","d":"easily understood","answer":"2","explain":" - Such of a way-> such a way","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Rudolph Nureyev has become one of the greatest dancer that the ballet world has ever known.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has become","b":"greatest","c":"dancer","d":"ever known","answer":"3","explain":" - Greatest dancer-> greatest dancers","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}